One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
"To Save His Daughter -
Kuma the Timid Pacifist"
Carry the seriously injured to the church!
Can somebody give us a hand?!
He's back!
It's awful... Our houses...
Why... Why did they do this?!
I won't forgive you, Bekori!
Wait, Kuma! That's enough!
You can't save anyone now!
Mommy!
No! No!
Hey, Kuma!
Come back! You're gonna die!
In a country far to the east,
this same approach was so successful...
...that the Celestial Dragons
praised their town...
...for being beautiful
and free of "garbage."
That's great!
For the sake of the people, the country,
and the immense happiness of the population,
we must sometimes be ruthless
and carry out reforms...
King Bekori!
Furious protesters have gathered
at the gate of the castle!
Murderers!
Stop it now!
Put out the fires in the south!
- Don't go any further!
- Back off!
Shoot four or five.
It's for the greater good.
No!
How could you do this?!
Those who dare defy the king's edict,
step forward!
Hm? Who's that?
Execute him right here!
Kuma's Church
Hurry and treat the wounded!
Bonney-chan, stay inside. You don't want
to be exposed to the moonlight.
Okay.
I hope he's safe...
Dad's always such a chicken.
W-Wait!
What do you want?!
Oh, I know! I'll grant you
all the area that I burned down!
I got rid of the human garbage!
Mommy!
Wait, you bastard!
You know what'll happen
if you attack the king!
You'll pay dearly for this!
The World Government won't
tolerate this atrocity!
You country-bumpkin pastor!
This incident would be known as the
Solo Revolution of the Sorbet Kingdom.
Holy Land
Mary Geoise
It appears the king of
the Sorbet Kingdom has been replaced.
That's strange. By whom?
Kuma! Kuma!
- King Kuma!
- Kuma!
Kuma! Kuma!
Unable to refuse the people's wishes,
Kuma became the king who kept
living in his old church.
King Kumachi!
My back hurts!
I think you can stop teasing me now.
It's Mr. Bulldog who is actually
running the country from the palace.
I'm just a figurehead
to make everyone feel secure.
Back in King Bulldog's day,
two generations ago, we were poor,
but we were spiritually rich.
Being poor was the pits though.
Oh? Where is Bonney-chan?
Oh, she is exercising there...
Oh? Where did she go?
Stamina! Stamina!
Have I ever seen that girl?
She looks just as pretty as Ginny!
What?! Ginny?!
Why are you all so shocked?
On my tenth birthday,
I'll sail out to the sea with Dad
and see the horizon!
What?! "Dad"?
So I'm building up stamina...
What?!
What?! You're Bonney?!
What was that transformation?!
Was it a Devil Fruit power?
When did you eat it?
Kumachi! Stay with me!
Maybe this is it... The Age-Age Fruit.
But where did she get it?
Try to make it happen.
Get older! Get older!
Wait, Bonney! I can't take it anymore!
King Kuma! Grant me an audience with you!
She really turned into an old bag!
Damn! She's full of wrinkles!
Look, Kumachi!
It's not working. I can't get older.
You're Princess Bonney, aren't you?
Who are you, old man?
I'm Bulldog. I'm an aide to your father.
Bulldog, Former King
(Two Generations Ago)
of the Sorbet Kingdom
I have something important to tell your father.
My mother is already here.
Conney, the former queen dowager.
Conney, Former Queen Dowager
- Our sincerest apologies!
- Sorry!
That's okay.
Look at this terrible rubbish!
"Evil Dictator"
It says Kuma burned down a village
and took the throne with violence!
Evidently, Bekori is behind this.
That bastard!
He's using a dirty trick while in exile!
He has the World Government on his side.
He'll come to take back the throne for sure.
There are reports of
warships being prepared.
No!
I don't want him back!
He'll have us killed this time!
We were finally able to live
with peace of mind.
I know. If he comes back,
I'll fight back
and destroy every force he musters!
But then I'll be branded as a criminal.
I won't be able to stay in this country.
When that happens, Bulldog-san,
I want you to take the throne!
I got bigger!
And I need you to shelter Bonney.
This church will be in danger.
- I did it!
- No problem.
I'll recreate this environment for her.
Thank you.
Bonney, I'll come back when I get a chance,
so be good.
That's my mother.
Bonney,
listen to Bulldog-san and Conney-san
and be good.
Are you going somewhere?
That makes me sad...
To protect you and everyone in this country,
I must go.
You've got some nerve coming back here!
That's him, Marines!
Kill him!
He took the Sorbet Kingdom away from me!
He's a tyrant who engages
in every kind of misrule!
Kill him!
I'm the king of this country!
Naturally, after sinking all the ships
and fleeing to the sea,
Kuma was placed on the wanted list as a pirate.
His numerous notorious deeds and his strength...
...drove up his bounty.
Bonney-chan.
The pizza is done.
I miss Dad...
I'm sorry, Bonney-chan.
Kuma-san saved this country, he's a hero.
I don't care! He's my daddy!
When I turn ten and get well,
I'll become a pirate, too!
You better not...
I can even become an adult right now!
From then on, Kuma traveled
all over the world...
...in search of a cure for Bonney.
Do you know this disease?
She can't be exposed to natural light.
What?! She can't be in the sun?!
How tragic...
There he is! A guy with a high bounty!
You're Bartholomew Kuma, aren't you?!
Your daughter...
...has five years at most to live.
She won't live to see her tenth birthday.
Come on!
Hey!
Kuma-chan! What are you doing here?!
Iva and Inazuma were imprisoned.
In our time apart, you've become
a king, a tyrant, and a pirate.
It's like I'm a totally different person.
No one in the Revolutionary Army
would fall for that article.
Hey, Kuma!
I wanna become the captain of the
Eastern Forces. What do you say?
Why are you asking me, Betty?
Dragon-san said until Kuma permits it,
it'd be held vacant in Ginny-sama's honor.
The Eastern Forces will be
led by a sharp-tongued woman?
I don't mind.
Ya-hoo! Hup!
Guys, here comes
the new captain of the Eastern Forces!
Sabo, Koala, and the others
are wishing to see you, too.
The young revolutionaries
are steadily gaining power.
I wish I could show it to you.
I'm happy for you!
I know you are.
It's great to have comrades...
I've seen what's happening in the world and
often wondered what you would have done.
I want to return to your army, but...
I wanted to talk to you about Bonney.
You know Dr. Vegapunk,
the Marines' scientist, right?
Yeah.
Seems like after the accident the other day,
he's going to move to a new lab.
He's normally not someone
you can easily meet,
but right now,
the security is evidently lax.
You think he can cure Bonney?!
Maybe...
He's an odd man,
but he's driven by his desires and trustworthy.
You should meet him.
- Take care, Kuma-chan!
- Bye, Kuma!
Thank you, Dragon!
To be honest, I had almost given up.
I'll go see him!
If Bonney gets better,
I want to fight with you again!
Let the winds of fate carry us
where they will, my friend.
Mm-hm!
- Bon voyage!
- Take care!
Let the winds of fate carry us
where they will...
Bonney! I'm back!
Dad!
You're so strong!
Well, I went easy on her...
How have you been?
Great! I'm building up stamina every day
so I can go out to sea at any time!
Good! Then let's go out to sea!
Really?!
Where are we?
Marines' Science Group,
Laboratory 8
(Later Known as Egghead)
We're seeing a doctor to get a checkup
before your disease is healed.
W-What?!
I-I've never seen anyone like you before!
I was thinking the same...
What a magnificent build!
Let me study your muscles!
In the name of science!
Hey, Dad! Let me see!
Look at that head. Gross...
Is she the sick girl?
What a sassy brat.
I don't hate it though.
Oh, Sapphire Scales, huh?
You've done well
to keep it from spreading more.
What do you think?
It's curable!
Are you sure?!
Yeah...
Yay! Yay! Yay!
I'll be using technology
not yet introduced in clinical medicine!
Specifically, I'll create stem cells
and transplant them.
But to do so, it'll require a lot of time
and money, like creating a cyborg.
Is she gonna become a cyborg?!
It'll cost as much, I said!
Are you a Buccaneer?!
Yeah.
Hey, I'm on the Government's side!
I trust Dragon.
What makes my blood different from others?
I don't have enough samples
to explain that in detail, but...
My clones?!
That's right!
I've been looking for the right person
to be the base for my clone soldiers!
If you donate your blood and give me
permission to create clone soldiers,
you won't have to pay for
the immense cost of Bonney's procedure.
You don't have money, right?
I won't decline that offer either way,
but can I ask what they'll do?
There'll be soldiers who look like me,
and they'll work for the Marines?
That's the idea!
Do you like electromagnetic energy?
If a human being shoots laser beams,
it'll shock pirates speechless!
We'll use our overwhelming scientific power
to defeat the rascals!
The sturdy bodies of my soldiers will act
as shields to repel bullets and save the weak!
They'll become heroes!
And furthermore,
the mighty warriors from the future will...
Dragon said what?!
He said you were an odd man, but you were
driven by your desires and trustworthy.
Is that what he said?
What a whipper-snapper!
If a clone soldier in my likeness
saves someone's life one day,
then maybe my being born
wasn't for nothing.
Dragon will be furious about these terms.
Well, I have nothing
but gratitude for you both.
To be honest, if Bonney could survive,
I wouldn't have cared if you were a devil.
Please save Bonney!
You're a true saint.
Clone soldiers are weapons.
And weapons are judged
by how many people they can kill.
Vegapunk would let a golden opportunity
slip through his fingers.
But I have a plan.
Yes, sir! I'm at your command!
A saint?
I'm just a timid pacifist who wants peace.
I like that!
I'll use that as the name for
the warriors of the future!
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY makerenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedzukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kidzuita no